费克雷 谢谢
Thanks, Fikret.
早啊 肯
Hey, Ken.
我就是想在这里润滑润滑 欢迎你回家
Just wanted to be on hand to smooth and say welcome home.
这些人是谁
Who are they?
附加人力 为了帮你更好适应新角色
Uh, additional manpower for the new role.
好吧 欢迎你们 “附加人力”
Okay. Welcome, " Additional manpower."
除非我需要 他们可以滚了
They can fuck off until I need them.
我只想露个面 跟老头们打个招呼
I just wanna show my face, check in with the grays,
然后就上飞机
and then get to the plane.
好吗 我想花更多时间在另一边
Yeah? I'd rather have more time other end, okay?
当然  -也许我早点到
For sure.   -Maybe I get in early
在马特森早餐的肉丸子里 塞一只米老鼠
and fucking slip a Mickey in Matsson's meatballs
好的 我们会确保
Okay, we'll make sure
飞机准备好起飞了
the plane is ready to go.
起飞之前 要不拍一张你和罗曼的照片
Before takeoff, might be nice to get a shot of you and Roman
抓拍就行 主题就是“登上舞台”
on the, uh, candid shot. " Stepping up."
“总裁兄弟“是次要选项
" CE-bros " Is kinda the bad version.
我们就别用次要选项了吧
Shall we, maybe, not do the bad version?
同意
Agreed.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
谢谢
谢谢你 兄弟 你有戏剧效果的天赋
Thank you. Boy, yoUhave a knack for the theatrics.
握个手吧
How about one of these?
你睡了吗
You get any sleep?
睡了一会儿 你有常听助手吗
Uh, a little bit. Did you get the condolence assistants?
有
Yeah. Uh-huh
你觉得怎么样 元老们 把我们推上前
What do you think? Old Guard, loading us up
戴着人类监听设备
with human listening devices?
好吧 你们这些笨蛋
All right, look at you fucking chumps.
是的  -这就是罗曼首发队吗
Yeah.   -This the Romey A-Team?
这就是我的团队了
This is the team.
你还好吗 你昨晚在这儿凑合睡的吗
What's shaking? You camp out overnight out here?
是的 我来得早 听他们汇报
Yeah, I got here early, I'm just getting briefed.
我叫小西进来吗?
Should I get Shiv?
巴斯蒂安 你能叫一下小西吗
Uh, Bastian. Could you get Shiv, please?
好的 所以 发生了什么
Okay, so what's bubbling?
你懂的 精简头条有哪些
You know, short-range top-lines?
工作室希望今早能开个电话会 是紧急事件
Studio would like to schedule a call this morning, red flag
我们同意重拍"利刃电子争霸"[电影] 气氛很焦灼
We're okay ing Kali spit ron re shoots, panicky vibes.
副制片人签了休假申请
Second producer signed off on leave
说他“精神过载及崩塌”
citing " Mental collapse slash overload."
我们同意了
Uh-huh. We okay it.
是吧 我们已经投入很多了
Yeah? We're balls deep already.
是的 我觉得我们得继续投钱
Oh, yeah, I think, gotta keep spending
虽然我会说很多次"不行
I will say " No " A lot,
还可能会大喊大叫 你们理解一下吧
and shout, obviously, initially, but yeah
你收到我发的邮件了吧
And you got my email
关于 马特森角度的交易想法
on Matsson angles, deal thoughts?
收到了 哪一封 你发了好几封
Yeah, which one? You sent several.
最后一封 “以此为准”
The last one. " Ignore previous emails
真好 谢谢你让我经历这一切
Yeah, great. Thanks for putting me through all that
顺便一提 兄弟们 我们这儿没事了
We're good here, by the way, guys.
是的 谢谢你们  -你们可以滚了
Yeah, thank you.   -You can all fuck off. Yeah.
好  -雨果 别跟我团队搭话
Great. Okay.  -Don't talk to my team, Hugo
那么 飞机上再聊  -好的
So, uh, talk on the plane?   -Yeah
又来了 “帝企鹅"进军了[法国纪录片"帝企鹅日记”]
Oh, here we go. March of the Emperor Penguins
早上好  -早上好
Morning.   -Morning.!
早上好  -欢迎回来
Morning.   -Welcome back, huh?
谢谢你  -恭喜
Thank you.   -Congrats
没什么好庆祝的 但是...  -是的
Nothing to celebrate, but...   -Yeah.
所以 现在是干嘛 你们在重新面试
So, what is this? You guys are re-interviewing
你们的职位吗  -不只 是在去挪威之前检查一下
for your jobs?   -No, just a check-in pre-Norway.
好的 我觉得我们在董事会电话会上检查过了
Oh, okay. I think we did the check-in on the board call,
还有之后的电话会 还有你发的三万三千封邮件
and on the follow-up call, and with your 33,000 emails
任何我们能帮上忙的地方
Well, just anything we can do to be helpful
关于 比如
In terms of, like, uh
模拟一遍谈判 或者...
dry-running the-negotiation or.
那好 来吧 “我们无条件信任你们”
Uh-huh. Okay. " We trust you absolutely.
但 现在 告诉我们 你们打算对他说的每一个字
now tell us every single word you plan on saying to him."
听我说 我们想彻底解决问题
Look, we wanna knock this out of the park
每股多个三四美元
Squeeze an extra three, four dollars a share
罗曼 我 小西都准备好了建议和沟通
Rome and me. Shiv on point here to advise and liaise
是的 我错过邀请了吗
Oh, cool, yeah. Did I miss the invite?
闲聊什么呢 婴儿潮一代和视频会议一代
Uh, what's the conf lab? Boomers versus Zoomers?
不是 小西 这没提前约
No, this is unscheduled, Shiv
老爸老妈路过
Mom and Dad just stopped by
确认我们冰箱里有吃的
to make sure we have food in the fridge
好的 马特森
Uh, okay, Matsson
在问...他..他说别慌张
uh, asking... he's... he's saying not to freak out.
什么  -慌张 为什么
What?   -Freak out, why?
什么 他犹豫了吗  -是
What, is he wobbling?   -Look..
你..你们都收到这个了吗 你收到了吗
Did... Did you al I just get this? Do you have this?
他们要所有人去
They're asking for everyone.
他们要求我们所有人 去挪威
They're requesting us all in Norway.
包括部门总经理 几位执行副总裁 我已经转发邮件了
plus division heads, bunch of EV Ps. I forwarded
实际上 他发送了一个名单
He actually sent a list of names.
好的 这他妈不是好兆头
Okay, so that's sinister as fuck
我们怎么看
What is it, do we think?
文化兼容性测试
Cultural compatibility check.
为时尚早 但这招挺巧妙的
It's early, but it is smart.
好吧 不过为什么要检测文化兼容性
Okay, but why check cultural compatibility
我们还没成交呢
if we haven't done the deal?
没准是因为我们真的要交易了呢
I guess because we are probably doing the deal?
是个好信号
It's positive.
或许他是在钻空子 想搞黄交易
Unless he's looking for a way out
是的 又或许是邀请所有人 这样他就不用只面对
Yeah, or invite everyone so he doesn't just have to deal
空镜两兄弟 我能看看名单吗
with the B-roll brothers? Can I have a look at this list?
可以 你们应该都收到邮件了 我看…
Yeah, yeah, you should all have it, I se..
你...你在名单上  -不 你没有发给我
You... You're on the list.   -No, you didn't send it to me
如果我们拒绝去 看起来会是怎样呢
What does it look like if we say no?
我们不扮演弱势的一方
We don't play that weak?
我觉得 为了完成交易
Um, I guess in the interest of doing the deal
我们都想要的交易
that we all want
也许我们应该 你懂的 跟他们合作
maybe we should, you know, play ball
对的 不 好的
Yeah. No. Great. Great. Good
咱们去拿下交易吧
Let's go get the deal
拿下  -让瑞典佬们放点血吧
Get it.   -Let's bleed the Swede.
继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 5 集
先生
Sir! Sir!
一切来得太快 就像龙卷风 是吧  -确实
Whirlwind, huh?   -Uh-huh
所以 为什么是挪威不是瑞典  -年度峰会
So, why Norway, not Sweden?   -Annual retreat.
不管怎么说 挪威和瑞典有什么区别
Anyway, Norway, Sweden, what's the difference?
都是从强暴主义者退化而来
It's all descended from the same rapists.
你好  -也是
Hey!   -Right.
你好  -好久不见
Hello.   -Hey, how are ya?
很兴奋可以感受 斯堪地那维亚
Well, excited to get a feel for Scandinavia and.
还有辣妹们  -辣妹
and some hotties.   -The hotties?
北极狐
The Arctic foxes.
一些挪威的森林  -格雷格
Bit of Norwegian wood.   -Greg?
什么  -放尊重点
Huh?   -Show some respect.
格雷格 我们不是去古根海姆博物馆参观
It's not a trip to the Guggenheim, Greg.
而是接受音乐电椅死刑
It's musical electric chairs
看看收购后 他们会不会喜欢我们
To see whether they like us after the acquisition.
看看他们喜欢谁
Find out who they like,
大家 欢迎来到石灰池[人掉进去会死]
everyone else, welcome to the lime pit
顺便一提 你坐另一架飞机
You're on the other plane, by the way
是的 我知道 谢谢 雨果
Yeah, I know. Thanks, Hugo
但…但是你不焦虑 对吗
But... But you're not worried, right?
我吗 完全不  -你应该还好
Me? No.   -You're good.
只要泛美网科没事 我不焦虑马特森
With the ATN carve out, I'm not worried about Matsson.
我焦虑的是
I'm worried about being whacked
被那边的龙蛇小霸王分队暴击
by the cast of Bugsy Malone over there.
汤姆 你有意见吗  -没有
You got a problem, Tom?   -No
你们真的不在意
You guys are seriously not concerned
老爸的黑料吗 因为还有更多在冒出来
about this Dad stuff? 'Cause there's been more.
抱歉 我得专注
Sorry, I have to focus.
工作室预算超支 “利刃电子争霸:冬眠”
Studio overages, Kali spit ron : Hibernation
两亿两千五百万 沉没成本
225 mil sunk cost.
预计三周重新拍摄
Estimating about three weeks of re shoots
大概花费两千五百万 还有三维电脑动画
which is like 25 mil, plus CGI
这他妈的 就是个 在洞穴里沉睡的机器人
It's a fucking sleepy robot in a cave,
怎么会花2.5个亿
how is that a quarter of a bill?
我是说 就是.. 你懂的 我就是
I mean, it's just... You know, I'm just struck
被背刺老爸的黑料数量 惊到了 还有...
by the number of pieces that knife Dad and.
暗示他的孩子们 尤其是他的小儿子们
and imply that his children, particularly his younger sons,
替他挡枪有一段时间了
have been covering for him for quite some time.
雨果   -怎么了
Hugo.   -Yeah?
如果有人在发老爸的黑料
Hey, if someone's briefing anything against Dad
我们就搞死他 好吗
we'll fucking crucify them. Okay?
搞死臭老鼠 好吗  -好的
Rat fucker Sam, okay?   -Okay
小罗 你想一起做马特森的
Rome, do you want to do the Matsson dossier together
多角度档案吗
for angles, yeah?
好的 一起做吧
Yay. Let's do it.
其实 我也不是很介意
You know, I don't... I don't actually care
如果你们想
If you want to..
抹杀掉 爸的传奇的话…
burn Dad's legacy or..
小西 我们正在努力地理解他的想法
Shiv, we're trying to prep to get inside his head
把这破玩意的油水榨干
to squeeze every nickel out of this fucking thing
还要保证 五个部门的数据 都他妈是合理的
and keeping the numbers straight across five fucking divisions
就是说...  -小西 我们…
it's just...   -Shiv, we're... we're...
我们在和食人魔生死搏斗
We're death wrestling with ogres
你们正在做的
You're reading documents
就是在读文件 肯
is what you're doing, Ken.
对了 有件事.
You know, one thing.
如果你希望 说出来就好
If you want, just to mention it.
什么  -我们可以嘎了汤姆
What?   -We can cut Tom's throat
好吧 他现在怎么样
Oh, well. Yeah, how's he doing?
他做得不错 做得挺好
I mean, he's doing good, he's doing fine
这不是重点 我们只是想
That's not it, we just thought, maybe
也许献祭他 会让你开心
in case that might be a nice thing for you
谢谢 你们真是太贴心了 想这样为我
Oh, well, thanks. So nice of you to offer that
其实吧 投资者会议那堆破事
Uh, you know what? I'm up to my fucking eyeballs
把我忙得团团转
in investor conference shit
我该去跟格丽聊一聊...或者…
so I should speak to... Gerri or..
但我个人认为 我们正在被
I happen to think we're being acquired
一家高水准的组织收购
by a high-caliber organization
就要出来结果了...  -我不知道
That's coming out...   -I don't know, guys
我想说 有很多值得钦佩的地方
I would say there's a lot to admire.
你们看到了吗
Yeah, did you see?
他们的媒介副长 是跳台滑雪运动员
Their deputy of comms is a ski jumper.
前冬奥会选手  -对我看到了
Ex-Winter Olympian.   -Yeah, I saw.
跳台滑雪运动员
A ski jumper.
你连站起来都费劲 你完蛋了
You can hardly stand up. You're fucked
富布赖特项目跟着他们的屁股跑
I mean, Fulbright s coming out of their ass
纳斯达克大师赛
NASDAQ master race
他们是一群令人印象深刻的
They're just a bunch of really impressive
非常有前途的年轻人
very serious young people.
当他们收购那个电子游戏发行商时
Did you see what happened when they acquired
你们知道发生了什么吗
the video game publisher?
不到百分之十的雇员留存率
Less than ten percent retention
他们像火蚁一样 掠过那个地方
They went through the place like fire ants.
绝对的精英制度
Incredibly meritocratic.
狭隘 怪异 残忍的混蛋
Insular, weird, brutal motherfuckers
我们死定了
And we're dead
行了 大家听着
Hey, come on, guys, listen
当然 他们年轻又健康
Sure, they're young and they're fit
可他们是欧洲人 他们软弱
but they're European, they're soft.
安心地躺平在 他们健全的社保网中
Hammock ed in their social security safety nets.
对长假和免费医保感到庆倦
Sick on vacation mania and free health care.
他们以为自个儿是海盗 没想过 我们可是被狼养大的
They may think they're Vikings, but we've been raised by wolves.
感染了一种名叫"洛根·罗伊"的病原体
Exposed to a pathogen that goes by the name Logan Roy
他们并不知道 即将要迎接的是什么
And they have no idea what's coming to them.
知道了吗
Okay?
我们是坐飞机的蛇
We're snakes on a plane
你们知道他是个电影迷吗
You guys clock that he's a movie guy?
我们可能需要统一口径
We might need a line.
以防他对工作室有疑问
In case he queries the fucking cash incinerator
就是那个“焚钞取暖炉”
that the studio is right now
这个安全带 怎么这么他妈的紧
Why's this fucking belt so fucking tight?
像是要勒死我
It's like strangling me.
你紧张吗 肯
You nervous, Ken?
不紧张 他只是个普通人
No, I mean, he's just some guy
好冷酷哦
Wow, the ice man.
我不知道 我可能对交易有点焦虑
I don't know, I mean, maybe a little anxious about the deal.
当然了
Sure.
你没问题 你很棒的
You're all right, you're good. Just, you know
你榨取的每一美元 都会让我们
fucking every dollar you squeeze makes us stronger
做皮尔斯-泛美网科的时候更有力
for when we do Pierce-AT N. Yeah?
外面可能有点小雨
Might be a little wet out there.
看看怎么样吧 谢谢你
but let's see how it goes. Thank you
期待见到你的冬奥会运动员吗
Looking forward to meeting your Winter Olympian?
安德烈亚斯·布洛克吗  -是的
Oh, Andreas Bloc?  -Yeah
在索契冬奥会的时候去掉了
The guy blew a seven-point lead
七分领先优势的那个运动员吗?  -我操
at the Sochi Winter Games.   -Fuck
他可能是个 太紧张就表现不佳的运动员 雷
He's a possible choker, Ray. Possible choker.
让他紧张起来
Choke him out.
那么...  -我们应该怎么走
So...   -Uh, where should we go?
去马特森主席的“再教育营" 应该怎么走
Which way to Chairman Matsson's re education camp?
请上车 就在下一站
Take a sea t. It's the next stop
我们就要出发了 还要等两件行李
We're about to leave. Two more bags coming
小西 这里挺棒的吧
Shiv. Pretty nice, huh?
我的运动鞋已经蹭上泥了
I already got fucking mud on my sneaks.
很棒  -你喜欢这些东西吗
Nice.   -You like the merch?
是的 我要一边盯着你
Yeah, I'm gonna jerk off over it
一边对着它们打飞机 你喜欢吗 小贱人
while staring at you. You like that, you little bitch?
我看得见你
I see you.
往窗外看 那是你吗
Look out your window. Is that you?
当然是我了 帅气的我
Yeah, of course it's me. The hand some one.
你的屋子小吗 我的屋子真他妈的小
Is yours small? Mine is fucking small.
如果有头熊在树林里拉屎 它用的可能就是这里
When a bear shits in the woods, it uses one of these, I think.
在 回头再聊   -好的
Yeah. Let me call you back.   -Yeah, great
各部门的领导等等 都被邀请去享用早午餐
Um, so, divisional heads,et cetera, are offered brunch
马特森邀请了谈判团队
and Matt son's invited the negotiating team,
也就是 “最高层们“ 洽谈
like, " Up top " to get into it
如果你想 他们会护送我们
and they'll escort us if you want.
好的  -好
Yep.   -Okay.
你想要再过一遍演示稿吗
Hey, you wanna walk the deck once more?
谈谈不同的角度 可预见的 各种可能
Talk the angles, the foreseeable unforeseen s?
不用了
No, we're good
计划的很好  -好的
Good on the plan.   -Okay.
没错 每个人都有一个计划
Well, yeah, everyone has a plan
除非他们被打了一拳
until they get punched in the mouth
可我...可我...我想补充一句
But I... but I... I might just add
我见过有人进去
I've seen guys going in,
采用强硬的方式
uh, you know, uh, playing hardball.
然后 就没有回旋余地了
and then not being able to row back.
所以你们的… 跟你们说 你们的父亲他会…
So your... I tell you what, your dad, now he..
通常 他会以一个笑话开头
Often he would just start with a joke.
只是确立 无论事情多糟糕
Just to establish that no matter how tough things are...
就这么个事吧  -是的
That's the whole thing, right?   -Yeah.
提出低于144的报价
Bring in an offer lower than 144
结果就是不开心 超过144 结果就是开心
net result, unhappiness. Over 144, net result, happiness.
是的 这种快乐会随着每一美元的增加而暴增
Yes, increasing exponentially with each additional dollar
直到 卡尔射湿了他的裤子
until such time as Karl creams his pants
然后 背着他的金色降落伞[高额离职补贴] 扬长而去
while dropping into his golden parachute.
好吧  -目标是147 希望能达到148
All right.   -Aiming for 147, hoping for 148
综合考虑 我们定在145或146就最好
What-with.everything, we'd settle for 145, 146.
对吗  -没错
-Right?  -Right.
这场游戏 就是这样吧  -小罗
That's the-whole of the game?   -Rome?
你好 老康  -我在弗兰克 E ·坎贝尔葬礼教堂
Hey, Con. -Uh, I'm at Frank E.Campbell.
然后.....现在不太方便
And, uh...   -Yeah, now is not a good time.
你们方便说话吗
Look, are... are... are you guys okay to talk?
因为 玛西娅来了
Because, uh, Marcia's been in
她一直在说 要给爸穿上苏格兰短裙
And she's talking about putting him in a kilt
就像"贝城偷心贼"[苏格兰乐队]那种风格  -什么
like a fucking Bay City Roller.   -What?
是老康的电话 说玛西娅来了
It's, uh, Con. Uh, Marcia's been in,
他们在讨论 给老爸穿苏格兰短裙 或者…
and they're talking about Dad with a kilt or s.
什么  -是的
What?   -Yeah.
他自己不能搞定吗
Can't he just fucking figure it out?
这是个闹剧吗 听着像
Is it just drama? It sounds like.
听着像个闹剧  -对 我听得到 肯
It sounds like drama.   -Yeah yeah, I heard that, Ken
我现在忙得不可开交
You know, I got a pretty full plate here.
知道吗 我刚才不得不取消了
Okay? I just had to cancel on a room full
和克利夫兰满满一屋子白人工人的会议
of working-class Whites in Cleveland
听着 我是真的担心
So, look, I am genuinely concerned
他会看着古怪 我会被怪罪
that he will look odd and I'll be blamed.
好吧 老康
Uh, okay. Hey, Con?
我们很感激 你帮我们控制局面
We appreciate yoUholding it down for us
可你需要我们做什么
but, uh, what do you need from us?
全权委托 如果我能走进
Carte blanche. If I go in the..
太平间 并且使用我的影响力
embalming room and start throwing my weight around
我会提出一些要求
I'm going to need to make some asks
可我不想被怪罪
but I don't want to get blamed
别让他们取笑你  -当然 可以的 老康
Don't let them make fun of you.   -Uh, sure. Okay, Con.
全权委托 你被授权了
Carte blanche, you're empowered
不会相互指责
No recriminations.
如果...如果你想发照片过来 或者什么的
If... If you want, send photos or whatever
不要发...发照片吗
Don't. S... Send photos?
他又不是带爸去海滩度假
He's not taking him to the fucking beach
不要发照片过来 好了 再见 挂了挂了
Don't send photos. Okay, bye. Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye
请给我一份华夫饼 谢谢
Um, can I have a, uh, waffle, please?
看上去不错
Looks good.
这是肉桂卷吗
Cinnamon buns?
确实 正宗的北欧盛宴
Oh, yeah. Serious Scandi spread here.
十分感谢
Thank you so much.
哦吼 这又是哪出
Uh  -oh. What's this, guys?
是埋伏 你咬了钩儿 养肥了该杀喽
Ambush. You took the bait. Fattened for the kill
各位好啊  -诸位 好运
Hi! Thank you.   -Good luck, everybody
你好  -弟兄们好
Hello.   -Hey, gang
是艾芭吗  -是我
Ebba?   -Hi.
下午好[丹麦语] 我代表媒介公关部
God efter mid dag. Comms and Public Affairs
你是卡洛丽娜  -对 是我
Karolina.   -Yes, exactly
您今天状态不错 春风满面
You look well. Very refreshed
您好 我是汤姆
Hi. Tom.
您是奥斯卡·古德约翰森吗 我是汤姆  -是我
Oskar Gudjohnsen?  I'm Tom.  -Yeah
我知道你 西沃恩的丈夫
Oh, yeah, Tom. Tom of, uh, Siobhan
是的 还是泛美网科的负责人
Yeah. Yeah. And, uh, AT N.
所以 我和这次收购
AT N. So I'm not really.
其实没什么关系
I'm not really part of this whole situation
以及
and, uh, yeah.
如果您想深入了解我们这边
And if you want... if you want a little guide of our forest
遮天蔽日的韦斯达族林 那些黑暗的秘密
you know, the mighty oaks of Waystar and the deadwood
找我就行
just, uh, give me a nod
行 找你是吧  -找我就行
Okay. You're the guy.   -I'm the guy.
那好 很高兴见到你  -我也是
All right, good to see you.   -Yeah.
兄弟 别吃光了 给我们剩点
Hey, easy, buddy. Leave some for us
您来点吗 我可以分您一些
Oh, would you like some? I'm... I'm happy to share
我新陈代谢很快 因为我活力充沛
I, uh, I metabolize fast because I'm dynamic
安德烈亚斯吗 你好啊  -你好
Andreas? Hey, man.   -Hey.
他们说 你在索契冬奥会差一点点 就能
Oh, wow. They... They tell me that you nearly got a bronze
拿到铜牌了
at Sochi.
很久之前的事了   -真厉害啊
Another lifetime, you know.   -Yeah
差点就青史留名了 兄弟
Oh, man, that's... That's almost huge, man
就差那么零点一秒 真可惜啊
You know? Those darn tenths of a second, huh?
吃得开心
Tuck!
那家伙真不是东西
Guy's a dick.
你们好  -好啊 他在这儿呢
Hey.   -Hey, hey there he is.
看看你们 玩儿真的啊
Oh, wow, look at you all. Rolling deep, huh?
核心团队都来了啊  -确实
Rock Steady Crew.   -Yeah.
最近怎么样  -还不错
What's up? Hey.   -Oh, okay. Hi
你们都来了啊
You made it.
是啊  -哥们儿
Yeah.   -Hey, bro
他们来这几干嘛
The fuck are you doing here?
迫不及待来聊聊了 是啊 是啊
Keen to get into it.   -Yeah, yeah, yeah
我不太确定 我们该怎么问候
I'm not sure... What do we do here?
抱你 会让我惹上官司吗
Am I gonna get a lawsuit if I hug you or..
有可能 想试试看吗
May be. Wanna find out?
行
Okay.
你把弟克们全带来了
You, uh, brought the whole gang, huh?
这下子算不过你们了
Outmaneuvered me.
我就孤身一人
I'm solo, baby.
不带上乡里的老家伙
What, you guys scared to come and talk
你们几个都不敢来聊聊了是吗
without the village elders?
不是  -当然不是
No.   -No
我们没想着要以多欺少兄弟
No, we don't want to out man you, bro.
逗你呢  -开谈吧
I'm just kidding.   -Let's talk
说正经的 就咱们几个聊聊吧  -就我们 走吧
But seriously, can we?   -Just us. Let's do it.
行 走吧 走吧
All right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.   -Let's chat.
如果你们想的话
Hey, if you want.
去他妈的满嘴兄弟
Fuck him and his dude-bluff
感谢你们能来
Thanks for coming out.
多谢了  -确实
Appreciate it.   -Yeah.
我明白 这不是最好的时机
I know it's not ideal.
确实 不过
Yeah, well,
我父亲又不是昨天刚走
it's not like our dad died yesterday.
也过了好几天了
It was a couple of days ago, so.
幸好不是 你们在没熄火的宝马上
Well, at least you didn't find him yourself.
发现他的尸体
BMW still running
那一幕才是真的心理创伤  -对对对
That shit can be traumatic.   -Right. Sure, sure.
不为小卢卡斯伤心一下吗  -真遗憾
No sorries for Lukas?   -No, sure.
深表遗憾兄弟  -又不是比惨大赛
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, man.   -It's not a competition.
我听说 你那只独具时尚的队伍
Um, saw that your little, uh, kicky ball team,
好像得了个 什么奖来着
they won a thing. They did a win or something?
恭喜啊 是的是的 谢谢
Congrats on that.   -Oh, yeah, yeah. Thank you.
准备得蛮充分  -是啊
Good dossier.   -Yep.
想知道我这儿有什么关于你的事吗
Do you wanna know what I have on you?
说说看
Yeah
你想去
So, do you want to may be..
我们来聊聊日程安排..
Uh, so, what's the, in terms of schedule.
我想我们可以.
We were thinking we could, uh..
放轻松 就我们几个 慢慢说
Relax, guys. It's just me, we can talk
行吗
All right?
好  -行吗
Okay.   -Okay?
所以 这地方是个什么鬼 这是哪儿
So, what the fuck is this place? What is this place?
难道是给律师的女儿
Like, the fucking 50 K wedding mill
结婚用的婚宴工厂吗 拍婚纱照的地方
for lawyers' daughters? Bridal shots by the window?
我懂 这地方有点夸张
Yeah, I know, it's kind of bullshit
但 也...
But it's also..
有那么一点点酷 随便吧 我也不在意
People thi... Cool? I don't give a fuck, honestly.
说点正事吧 气氛都烘托到这儿了
Can we get into it? I feel like I want to say shit
言归正传 或者你们想等会儿再聊  -现在聊吧
Can we get into it? Or do you want me to wait?   -Yeah, yeah
聊正事吧 我们…
Yeah, yeah. Let's get into it. We, um.
我们来 是想说 我们很期待与你交易
We've come to say that, um, we like your offer
但是我们觉得 报价上
But we don't, as yet, think it reflects the full valuation
不能完全体现我们的价值
of the potential of what you're purchasing
行吧
Okay.
你们股价周五跳水了百分之二十
And your stock dropped 20 percent on Friday?
但周一就回升了百分之十
And regained ten Monday
好
Okay.
公司的未来规划 就没有计划要依托于洛根
Logan was never going to be part of the company going forward
从商业的角度上来说
I mean, in a business sense,
他的离去并不会改变什么
his absence is not relevant.
我们的核心增长点 不会受家父离世的影响
Our key growth drivers are unaffected
股价下调 只是正常现象 不代表什么
by our father's passing. The dip is the dip. It's not...
确实 但我还是觉得
Yeah, but I... I still feel like
像是门店甩卖期间去结账
I'm going to the checkout during a sale
却被要求 多给钱一样
and getting asked to pay more.
有点像的  -卢卡斯 144的报价如果在上周
A bit.   -Well, Lukas, if you were willing to pay 144 last week
股东都不会理你
shareholders won't like you
没得聊  -我能打断一下吗
looking opportunistic...   -Yeah, can I interrupt you
打断一下  -最好别.
right the re?   -I'd rather you didn't.
但你已经打断了 说吧
but you already did, so..
我想提出一个新的提议
I would like to propose... an offer.
我想收购整个集团
I want to buy your entire operation.
开价...
For the price... of one..
一美元
single dollar.
逗你呢  -笑死
I'm kidding.   -That's really good.
真好玩啊
That's funny.
一美元呢 呵呵  -抱歉
One single dollar. Ha ha.   -Sorry.
兄弟 你的脸色太好笑了
Sorry, man, your face was...
但我确实想要泛美网科
But I... I... I do want A TN though.
不行 泛美网科免谈 爸把它划出去了
Well, no. AT N's off the table. Dad carved it out
我知道 但我觉得这不合理
Yeah, I... I'm not sure it makes sense.
我想把它要回来  -何出此言
and I want it back in.   -Uh, why?
原因吗  -为什么
Why?   -Why?
原因啊
Uh, why?
我觉得 不言而喻了啊 对吧
I feel like I don't have to say why, do I?
开始就是这么打算的
It's the original deal.
我们有现成的规划
Like it's... it... We have the shape.
一切犹如 顺水推舟
This can be fast.
你们会不虚此行 很快尝到甜头
You can get the sugar that you came looking for
报价呢
The price is what?
还没到报价的时候吧
Oh, I don't think we're at price.
187美元一股
Like, 187 per share.
一半股权置换 一半现金
Fifty  -fifty cash stock..
全部买下
for the whole thing.
你们不准备聊聊有什么想法吗
Are you gonna tell me what you think?
当然 当然要
Yeah, yeah, sure.
要聊  -行 你们可能没经验
Sure.   -All right, maybe you guys haven't done this before,
一般情况下 我开口之后...
but how it usually works is I say something.
你们也得开口
and then you say something
因为 如果你们不开口的话
Cause if you don't say anything, some things
事态就有点僵化了
tend to get a bit congealed.
我打断一下 去你妈的
Can I interrupt you? And say fuck off.
建议得真他妈专业啊  -行
Yeah, thanks for the pro tip.   -Okay.
你知道的 我们并没有
Yeah, we just weren't, you know,
预料到这个情况
we weren't expecting that
所以 不能确定是否可行
And, Uh, I'm not sure that that works
可行的  -这个
It works.   -Okay.
我们不确定是否可行
Yeah, well, we're not sure that it does work
可行的
It works.
你..你们是不是想跟外面那些老人家商量一下
Do... Maybe you want to check in with the boiled eggs out there?
是的 这是个很大的变化
Well,yeah, this is a material change
我们得...  -当然 当然
We need to...   -Of course, of course.
你说得对 百分之百
All that. Hundred percent, um..
但是 你们喜欢这个提案吗
But do you like it?
我们私下说
Just between us.
你有一点点喜欢 对吗
Oh, you like it a little bit, don't you? Right?
还是有点可谈的余地 对吗
There's something there, huh?
你不用回答 但是...
You don't have to answer but.
给点提示可以吗
may be an indication.
喝点香槟如何
A bit of bubbles?
我觉得 我们要休息一下
I think we're just gonna take a beat actually
我们要...好吗
We're just gonna... Yeah?
我们等下继续  -好的
We'll talk later.   -Yeah
好吗
Okay?
太迫切了
So fucking eager.
我们说实话 对吗  -是的 说实话
We say? Yeah?   -Yeah, we say.
他给的价格是187
Hi. So the offer is 187
但是 其中包含了泛美网科
but he wants AT N
他…他在那  -好吧
He's... He's right there.   -Okay, well
你能别这么兴奋吗 卡尔
why don't you tuck your boner away, Karl?
但他是想促成这次交易的 对吗  -是的 他想交易
But he wants the deal?   -Yeah. He wants the deal
我觉得 他知道泛美网科是敏感话题
And I think he knows AT N is an emotive issue
他就是故意在搞我们心态
and he's being a fucking ass hole
当然 当然
Oh, sure, sure, sure.
但这是好消息 先生们
But excellent news, gents, huh?
天大的好消息
Excellent.
你们把价格抬高了不少
You effectively achieved a bump
是的 我们很棒 我们太厉害了
Yeah, we did amazing. We're amazing people
那 我们直接跟董事会汇报
So we take it to the board
是的 首先 我们要算一遍
Yeah, well, first, we have to run through it
确保价格可行  -小西在哪
and make sure it works.   -Where's Shiv?
她下去了
Oh, she went back down.
好吧 我们得跟她讨论一下
Okay, well, we should talk to her too
是的 我们一起去吧
Yeah. Let's go do that
太好了
Excellent.
你觉得 他是在逗我们玩吗
You think he's just trying to fuck with us?
他到底是真的想要泛美网科 还是说 他想被
He actually wants AT N, or is this a move
我们回绝 然后压低价格的策略
so that we ask to subtract, and he goes low?
谁在乎他 我们想要什么 才是最重要的
Who cares? What do we want?
我们当然是想留下泛美网科的 对吗
Well, we want to keep it, right?
我们完成老爸的交易 保留泛美网科 加上皮尔斯
We do Dad's deal, keep AT N, we add PGN
你和我 还有小西 三贱客 共同掌权
And you, me, and Shiv, you know. The Three Fuck a teers. Hey
我刚刚听到了一个不怎么样的谣言
Uh, so, I just got a bad rumor in my ears.
是什么 显然
What is it?   -Uh, apparently
泛美网科开了一条杰瑞德·门肯选举团的专线
AT N has an open line to Jeryd Mencken's campaign team
他们刚刚在编辑部的晨会上拨通了电话
and they're just dialed in on editorial morning conference.
你知道这个事吗  -我不知道
Did you know that?   -Uh, I did not know that
罗曼 如果这个消息传出去 会降低我们的信誉
Rome, if this comes out, this blows any credibility
好吧
Yep.
这样是不行的 罗曼  -对
That's not okay. Rome.   -Yeah.
我不知道 都怪希德 希德是主管
Yeah, I don't know, fucking Cy d. Cyd's in operational charge.
这是相互陷害  -罗曼 就连爸都有底线
It's a mutual back scratch.   -Rome, even Dad had a line.
小西 我们可以....我们应该.
Look, Shiv, we can... We should.
我们应该仔细讨论 这样确实不行
We should get into that, it's not okay.
但是
but, uh..
但是 我们得集中注意力
But we do need to focus
我们应该讨论一下更重要的事
Big picture, we should discuss
把泛美网科也卖了 怎么样
What do we think on AT N folded back in?
卖泛美网科吗  -是的
Uh, AT N back in?   -Yeah
靠 好吧 当然 打包出售
Fuck, uh, well, then, yeah. Sure, fine, get rid of it
这个资产有毒
It's a toxic asset.
但 爸引以为豪 而且他为了保住泛美网科命都不要了 对吗
Uh, it's also Dad's pride and joy, he died trying to keep?
是的 好吧 我们拿一件他的白毛衣留念也行
Yeah, well, let's just keep one of his old sweaters.
至少没那么种族歧视
Less racist.
我们要淡定一点 才显得有把握
You know, there's leve'rage in not looking too thirsty
他必须明白 如果交易不成功
He needs to know that if there's no deal
我们也很好 而且能再创辉煌
we're good, we survive, thrive
但 我们真的可以吗
But do we? Like, can we?
肯和我 工作做得还不错
Well, Ken and I have been doing a pretty good job
从天算起吗
In the last 24 hours?
价格也稳定 市场还挺喜欢我们的
Price has stabilized, markets seem to like us.
对啊 市场喜欢你们跟马特森交易而已
Yeah, the markets like that you're selling to Matsson
爸想保留泛美网科
Well, Dad wanted to keep A TN
是啊 他还想毒死勃列日涅夫
Uh, yeah, but he also wanted to poison Brezhnev
还有 吊死曼德拉
and... and hang Mandela.
这并不说明他是对的
It doesn't mean he's always right
我觉得 总体来说 他是想交易的 所以
I think that overall, he wanted the deal, so.
我们也不知道
Well, we don't know.
我们..我们不能被爸的计划牵着鼻子走
We... we can't navigate by Dad maps
他不在了  -我知道他不在了
He's not here.   -I know he's not here.
我的心灵被重创 无时无刻不在头痛..
I have a giant hole in my heart and a 24-hour migraine and
我只是想说 我们也不知道他是否..
I'm just saying, I don't think we know if.
会完成这笔交易 还是放弃这个交易
Would he have done the deal? Would he not have done the deal?
我们...我们不知道
We don't... Wel don't know
你知道吗 快点完事就好了
You know what? Just... Let's get it done.
我真的不...我不...随便吧
I don't really... I don't... Whatever.
尽快成交就行
Just get the deal done.
我们要巧妙地走好每一步
Okay, so we need to play this very delicately
就像 摆在你面前的是棋盘 每一步都至关重要
Laid before you is a chessboard, so every move is crucial
所以 你有什么消息
So what have you got?
马特森很冷酷
Matsson, pretty cold
对  -他还是无名小卒的时候
Right.   -When he's fucking randos,
就是个卖降噪耳机的
he does noise-cancelling headphones
好的  -播客
Right.   -Podcasts
他只要躺好 带上耳机 坐等看戏就行
He just lies back, can s on, watches'em slide the bean pole
好吧 我还是不确定
Okay. Well, I'm not sure
要怎样利用这一点
how I'm gonna use that to my advantage
有没有跟铁笼赛有关的消息
Um, and what about in terms of the cage fighting?
对 有人说 保管猎杀名单的人是艾芭
Yeah um, so some say Ebba, some say Oskar
有人说 是奥斯卡
in terms of who's keeping the kill list.
所以 真的有猎杀名单吗
Oh, so there is a kill list?
真的 有消息 很可靠
Oh,yeah, I have it on good authority
确实有猎杀名单  -好吧
There's a kill list. Yeah.   -Right.
大概有八九个名字 还在不断调整中
Like, eight, nine names. It's evolving.
好吧 我要去了 不管了 我需要刷存在感
Okay, I'm going in, fuck it. I need profile
但是 你得等我信号 好吗
But keep your eyes out, okay?
如果我需要你来当炮灰 我就给你使眼色
If I need a pawn sacrifice, I'm going to give you the eyes
好吗
Okay?
来一杯啤酒 谢谢
Uh, can I take a beer, please? Thank you.
银行那边 对这个数字亮黄灯
The bankers will, uh, give the number a yellow light,
所以 还是有操作空间的
so that gives us room for maneuvers
好吧
Okay.
格雷格  -你们还好吗
Hey, Greg,   -What's, uh, what's up?
谈判怎么样了
What's the counter?
什么 就是说
What?   -Just saying, yeah
如果 你们需要一起头脑风暴一下
in case you guys want to sling some ideas around
就是…在四人小分队内部
Just... within the safety of the Quad
四人队吗  -对 四人突击小分队
The Quad?   -Yeah, the Quad Squad.
罗...罗伊巡逻队 老队友们
The... the Roy Patrol. The... the old team
逆天的家庭战队
The fucking... the... da family
什么鬼
Da fuck?
也许 你可以给我倒杯咖啡什么的
Yeah, maybe you could get me a coffee or something
我只是...有种预感
I just... I got a feeling
你们好 你好
Hey.   -Hey!
建议我加入吗
Mind if I perch?
当然不 没问题  -那太好了
Sure. No problem,   -Yeah, great.
卢卡斯 你还记得 我们…
Lukas, you remember, we... we laughed
我们之前在太阳谷
We were at Sun Valley.
我们...我们一起嘲笑桑达的短裤
We... we were mocking Sundar's cargo shorts,
折痕 还有...
the creases, and the.
是的 是的  -对 没错
Okay. Yeah. Okay.   -Yeah. Yeah.
我们刚刚在讨论 法国能不能过这一关
Well, we were just discussing, Uh, is France gonna make it?
抱歉 是关于…比如...
Sorry, in terms of... As in... Like, the..
就像他们...法国能不能挺过去
As in, like, will they make... Will France make it?
出生率 青年失业率 僵化的体质
Birth rate, youth unemployment, sclerotic state, um,
惹恼愤怒的阿拉伯人 等等  -好吧
fucking angry Arabs, all that.   -Right.
他们能不能过这关 还是说 会像希腊一样
Will they make it, or will they pull a Greece?
我觉得...你需要知道的是
Well, what I.. I think what you need to know about..
一个美国新闻界的角度
from a... well, from a US news perspective,
那就是 我们根本不在乎
is that we really don't give a fuck
美国就像…
Uh, US is..
美国就像式微的帝国 我们不知道
US is late imperial, and we don't know.
因为我们也不想知道
Because we don't really wanna know
我们有自己的巴黎 如果烧坏了
You know, we have our own Paris, and when it burns,
我们就建另一座
we'll build another.
哇 汤姆
Wow, Tom.
你知道吗 我最近读了篇文章
You know, I, uh, I read a great article recently
在“经济学人“上  -什么“经济学人“吗
in The Economist about it...   -Oh,excuse me? The Economist?
求你了[法语] 再多告诉我们一点吧
S'il vous plait!! Tell us more.
不是.  -别停 继续说 继续
No, well.. yeah...   -No, no. Go on. Go on, go on.
法国的优势 仅仅是在教育
Just in terms of education and quality of life?
和生活品质方面吗 千万不要
Old Lady France? Fucking don't fucking bet
小看老法棍 你们懂的...
against the old fucking, uh... the... the baguette, uh, you know.
法棍可能比贝果
The... the baguette might be
更强大  -我能...对不起..你..
mightier than the bagel.   -Can I... sorry... who...
你是谁 我不记得名单上有你
Who are you? I don't remember you from the list.
我吗  -是的
Me?   -Yeah.
好吧 说来话长
Well, therein hangs a tale
我是格雷格·赫希 是格里格雷格里·赫希
Greg Hirsch. Or y. Gregory Hirsch
他是个表亲 他是洛根的侄外孙
He's a cousin. He's Logan's nephew.
等等 你是说真的吗
Wait. You serious?
他是我表弟 是个好人
He's my cousin. He's good.
还有...还有更多的亲戚
The re's... There's more of them.
还有…
There's...
等等 你们...你们..你们都是亲戚吗
Wait. Are you... You're... Are you all related?
这是一个巨大的 排外的...  -不是
This is one big, uh, insular...   -No, no.
不是的
No, no, no.
只有我们
Just us.
是的 你同意吗  -是的 说实在的我同意
Yeah, you agree?   -I do. I do actually
你们笑完了吗 还是…
Are you done, or...
我不知道 也许配上学幕会更有意思
I don't know, maybe it's funnier with subtitles
是的 对不起 兄弟对不起
Yeah. Sorry, man. Sorry.
没关系 我只是...我已经看够了这种场面
It's fine. I've just... I've seen enough of this shit.
但是你们..你们高兴就好
But, uh, yeah, you do... you do what you like.
是的 我们只是在消磨时间 等你还盘
Yeah, we're just passing time till you come up with a counter
你想在这里谈吗
You wanna do this here?
好吧
All right.
谢谢 肯  -没事
Thanks, Ken.   -Yeah.
让我们单独谈谈  -好的
Give us a minute.   -Yeah.
好了
Oka, well
我不想抢在董事会之前行动 但是…
I don't wanna preempt the board, but..
我认为...我们认为
my view... Our view...
这笔交易不一定有吸引力
it's not necessarily compelling.
我们正在统计数字
We're running the numbers,
但我们也在考虑 保留泛美网科的方案
but we want to explore options for us keeping ATN
好吧
Okay
不乐观  -我们只想听听
Bad   -We just wanna hear you
你对我爸的交易价格的看法 不包含泛美网科
on price for Dad's deal. No AT N.
你们并不想要泛美网科
You don't want ATN
好吧 确实 但我们还挺想要的  -你们并不想要
Okay, sure, but we kinda do.   -You don't.
我和奥斯卡谈过了 有翻盘的可能
I've been talking to Oskar, and we see a way back
有翻盘的可能
You see a way back?
好吧 好吧 你觉得我们
Okay. Okay. You see a way back for our..
利润丰厚 举足轻重的新闻业务 有翻盘的可能?
phenomenally lucrative and influential news operation?
你要拯救它吗
You gonna save that?
是的 它...  -谢谢你 兄弟
Yeah, it's...   -Thanks, bro.
它看似不错 但数据不容乐观
It's... It's fine, but the graph is horrible.
好吧 听着 我们只是
Well, look. We're just.
老实说 我们担忧的是
Honestly, we're concerned.
你的商业愿景是否合适
about the fit, about your vision.
我们一半的收益来自股票 五五分成
And with half our value coming in stock, 50-50 split,
如果你...搞砸了 我们会损失惨重
we stand to lose a lot of value if you... screw it up.
所以 情况很复杂  -不会..
So it's complicated.   -No…
并不复杂 我研究过
It's not complicated. I've seen it. It's, uh
很多身材矮小 青筋暴起的人 在大喊大叫
it's.. it's a lot of yelling. Small men, big veins
他们财力雄厚  -当然 但长远看来
Fat wallets.   -Sure, but long-term,
我不认为给愤怒的老人看的新闻有前途
I don't think news for angry, old people works
我不认为我会把它收入囊中提高播放流畅度
don't. I would fold it in. Fat pipe that shit.
色调改成彭博灰
Make it more Bloomberg grey. You know?
简单 实惠 大量
Simple, cheap, huge.
类似宜家的模式  -兄弟 我不得不说.
IKE A'd to fuck.   -Dude, I gotta say...
我想 你可能不明白 你买的是什么
I think maybe you don't understand what you're buying
也许 这就是为什么 我们会在价值认知上脱节
And may be that's why there's a disconnect here on value
确实 那你教我做事吧 沃尔特男
Oh, sure. Lecture me, Vaulter guy.
我刚教你了
Hey. Took a big swing
论经验
If you look at experiences,
这个值得信赖的品牌 所运营的
you look at the high ceiling on parks, cruises,
公园 游轮 豪宅 的标准都很高
IP-turbo ed-residential from a trusted brand.
你称它为”值得信赖的品牌"吗
Did you call it " A trusted brand?
是的  -是的
Yeah.   -Yeah.
不 不是 这是一家零件商店
No, no. It's a parts shop
零件都很好 没错 但品牌很差
Good parts, yes. Bad brand
我不得不说 你在本质上就错了
Gotta say, I just think fundamentally you're wrong
好吧 我不在乎你的想法
Yeah, well, I don't care what you think
你们只是一个翻唱乐队
You're a tribute band.
我们没矛盾吧
We okay?
是的 我们没矛盾 没矛盾
Yeah, we're okay. We're okay.
我只是 想让你们变得富有而已
I'm just trying to make you fucking rich
本来就富有
Already rich.
好的 好吧 在报价上 我认为…
Okay. Well, on the offer I think
我就是我 我就是我
I am what I am what I am.
好吧 大力水手 我们…
Okay, Popeye. We'll, uh
我们会跟进的 反馈给董事会
we'll check in, take it back to the board
行吗 我不想谈崩
Right? Hate to see this break down.
是的 全力以赴吧 全力以赴
Yeah, let's make it work. Let's make it work.
时间到了
Okay.   -All right, it's time!
该去桑拿了 桑拿 桑拿
Time for sauna. Sauna! Sauna!
来吧 桑拿 桑拿 桑拿
Come on. Sauna! Sauna! Sauna!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
可怜的家伙们
Poor bastards
像北京烤鸭一样 挂在橱窗里
Hanging in the window like Peking duck.
你好  -你好
Hey.   -Hey.
很抱歉 天公不作美
Sorry about the shit weather here
你应该上周来的
You should've been here last week
是的 上周一切都好很多
Oh, yeah. Well, everything was better last week
西沃恩 这是艾芭 我们的媒介主管
So, Siobhan, this is Ebba, our head of comms.
你好  -你好
Hey.   -Hi.
艾芭就像我们身边的
Ebba is like an estrogen air freshener
雌性空气清新剂 让我们
we keep around to try to keep us
闻起来更干净
uh... smelling clean.
没关系 我会记下的
It's okay, I keep notes
我离职后 他们要么贿赂我 要么被我写进书里
When I walk, it either goes in my book, or they pay me off.
你永远不会离职 你喜欢这份工作
You'll never walk. You fucking love it
是的 我喜欢
Oh, yeah. Uh-huh. I love it.
所以...事情…
So, uh... how bad was..
有多糟糕?
this thing?
这个吗？   -是的
This?   -Yeah.
高贵的雄鹿们耍着花拳绣腿吗
The majestic stags sparring with their memory foam hard-ons?
精彩的令人窒息
It was a breathtaking spectacle.
听着
Listen...
我是不太靠谱
I like to fuck around.
但我的不靠谱 仅限于
I do. But... but I like to fuck around like..
大清早 服用致幻剂
psilocybin at breakfast, you know?
好吧  -一旦牵扯到钱..
Uh-huh.   -When it comes to money, just.
开个价吧  -好吧
say the fucking number.   -Uh-huh
当然 那么 我算什么角色 信使女孩吗
Sure. So, what am I? The... the messenger girl?
还算数吗?
Is it there?
交易还算数吗
Fucking deal?
是的 可能吧
Yeah, potentially
可能还算数吧
It's potentially there.
你怎么认为
What do you think?
什么  -感觉如何
Hmm?   -How does it feel?
我不知道 感觉不是很好 但是..
Oh, yeah. I don't know. Not great, but...
我想 这就是问题所在 对吧
also, I guess that's the thing, right?
我们要卖...
We're selling. It's like..
但输赢还很难料
have we won or lost? It's kinda hard to tell
因为...
Because...
我想放弃这笔交易
I think I'd like to tank the deal
保留泛美网科吗
Keep ATN?
放弃整个交易
I think tank the whole deal
取消 全部叫停
Like, kill it. Blow it up
这个吞剑表演
Well, that's quite the high-risk
代价不小啊
piece of fucking sword swallowing
我喜欢掌舱 我觉得我们很擅长
I like running the ship. I think we're good at it.
我不想停 你呢
And I don't want to stop. I mean, do you?
所有人都想做成这笔交易 这是爸的交易
Well, everyone wants the deal. It's Dad's deal
马特森不适合
He's a bad fit.
是的  -你知道的 他不适合
Yeah.   -You know it. He's a bad fit
他不懂这家公司 肯定会搞砸的
He doesn't get the company and I think he's gonna fuck it
我们近距离接触过他 了他只是个纸牌魔术
We've seen him up close and he's a card trick
他会摧毁爸建立的一切
and he's gonna destroy everything Dad built
你想...想和小西聊一下吗
You want to, uh.. Wanna chew it with Shiv y?
是的
Yeah.
我只是觉得..  -什么
I just think...   -What?
小宝会周旋吗
Can Pinky dance?
不会 显而易见 但是…
I mean, no. Obviously not. But...
但你喜欢这个提议
You like it though
从周末狂欢者 摇身一变 成为全职主夫
Go from fucking weekend warriors to bossing full-time?
毕竟是老爹的交易
It's Dad's deal.
要不…要不就
It just... It feels.
该死 完成这笔交易吧 完成他的未竟事业
fucking do the deal. Finish his breakfast, you know?
我也不太清楚 你觉得他会怎么做
I don't know. What do you think he would do?
我觉得他会怎么做?  -对
What do I think he would do?   -Yeah
当然是照他想的那样去做咯 不是吗
Exactly whatever the fuck he wanted, right?
没错
Well, that's right
但后面的路 我们得帮他走下去 不是吗
Well, we have to make him walk, right?
让他以为 是他自己的主意
So that he thinks it's his call?
对
Yeah.
如果那帮老顽固 察觉到我们变聪明了 想耍诈
I mean, if the Old Guard smells that we're getting smart
铁定又会大发雷霆 跑到董事会那里去控诉我们
they're gonna shit their beans, go crying to the board
那时 我们就完了  -当然 没错
and we're fucking toast.   -Yeah. Sure.
就好比 在悬崖边上走钢丝
It's a fucking tightrope walk on a straight razor
一步不慎 就跌得粉身碎骨
Five-hundred-foot reputational drop
正是如此 你怎么还笑得出来
Okay, but why is that making you smile?
我不觉得这有什么好笑的
That shouldn't make you smile
谁没事喜欢在悬崖边上走钢丝啊
Who likes tightrope walking a straight razor?
你个疯子  -我只觉得我充满干劲
Nut bag.   -I just think it's fucking feel the force time
就好像是 进行一场冒险
Choose our adventure.
奋不顾身 彻底干碎他们
Full bore. Fuck the living shit out of this thing
你来不来
You with me?
好吧 就这么办吧
Yeah, let's do it.
彻底毁了交易 听你的
Let's tank it. Let's fucking do it
好
All right.
我有时候...很难理解别人的意图
I've... I can find it hard to see the angles on people
你知道吗
you know.
我 我...我很容易上头 然后..
Like, I... I... I get into things, and then..
我这个人…做事情很容易失去分寸
I don't have... I don't have very good boundaries
就好比...
Like..
我现在这样
I'm doing it now.
好吧 我认为...
Okay, so I think...
把价喊高点 你就会得到你想要的
a meaningful bump gets you over the line
我明白了 你的意思是.
All right. So you're saying..
只要我不停地出更多钱
if I keep offering more and more money..
到头来 就会如愿以偿
eventually, I'll get it.
谢谢你 小天才
Thanks, top mind
你终于领悟了
You got it.
你觉得艾芭怎么样
What do you think of Ebba?
不知道 无从开口
Yeah. I don't know
艾芭不太好
Ebba is not good
她总是
She's very...
对我很抗拒
Like she won't let me in.
你们家卡洛丽娜怎么样?  -她很不错
What's your Karolina like?   -She's good
她靠得住
She's solid.
给  -好
Here.  -Sure
我呢
Well, I...
我可能碰上了一点麻烦
I might be in a bit of a pickle.
怎么了  -对 大家对我 评头论足
Yeah?   -I  Yeah. People are judging me.
是吗  -对
Yeah?   -Yeah.
这样的评论铺天盖地
Lots of judging.
你和你丈夫之间怎么了
So, what's going on with your husband situation thing?
我们结束了
Well, we're fucked
简直是场灾难
It's a disaster
我伤害了他..
I broke his heart and.
他也伤害了我
he broke mine..
我们失去了彼此
and we lost our footing
我也不知道
I don't know.
我没法…
Hey, I'm not gonna...
跟你——讲前情提要 我只能说
give you the whole backstory and everything, but
之前...我在和一个女生交往
I was... I was seeing this girl
因为说了一些不好的话.
and after we broke up..
最后我们分手了
because of some things that we said
当时我们正处在热恋阶段
when things were nice and intense, you know
我开了一个很不合时宜的玩笑
as sort of a nasty, friendly joke about.
我的确不该那么做
about what I shouldn't do
我寄了点 我的血 给她
I sent her some of my blood
好吧
Okay.
大概半升 冷藏的血
A half-a-liter frozen blood brick
很明显 我想开个玩笑  -半升吗
As a joke, obviously.   -Half a liter?
对
Yeah.
然后... 我认为 这当然
And then... Well, I mean, obviously
首先 很不错的故事,  -当然
first of all, good one.   -Yeah.
我给她寄血的时候 她认为有点奇怪 但是我
Well, she got a bit weirded when I did that, but I,
后来一直给她寄血 一次又一次
I just kept doing it. Again, and again, and again.
之后 就不再是一个玩笑了
And then, it... it became not a joke..
然后 又有点好笑
and then a joke again.
但 现在看来.. 又没那么好笑了
And... and now, it's... apparently not a joke.
这实在..
This is...
那么 这个女孩是谁
Well, who is this?
艾芭
It's Ebba.
其实 是艾..
Actually, it's...
是的 这有点 有点…
Yeah. It's a bit... It... it's a bit, uh.
情况有点复...复杂
A com... complex situation
但是...我可以完全
But what... I'll... I'l I just..
不认账 对吧
deny it, right?
我可以说 她血口喷人 然后让律师摆平一切
I'll call bullshit and just lawyer it out
否认 有点不太现实
Well, Deniability is difficult
鉴于 她手上 还有那么多你的血
given she has so much of your blood
伙计 这可是你的媒介主管
Man, your head of comms?
我不知道是谁给你出的这些主意
I don't know who you got advising you on this
但是 不管他们跟你说了什么
but whatever they're telling you
你都得拿出十倍的精力去对待
you gotta 10x it.
因为你也清楚的 公众还不了解你
Cause people, you know, people don't know you,
如果这次收购成功的话
and if this acquisition goes through
全国媒体都会抓着你不放
US media are gonna be all over you.
如果挖出来说 你是一个变态跟踪狂
So if you're the creepy stalker guy
是一个躲在黑暗里 一边敲键盘
who sits in the dark writing code
一边输液的程序员
dripping into an IV bag.
还骚扰直接下属的话
and harassing his direct reports, it's
对经济收益肯定会有影响
it's gonna have an economic impact
太糟糕了
It's bad.
我有三个公关建议 可以给你参考一下
Well, three-point PR plan just off the top of my head
第一步
Point one
对你来说 可能有点困难
Might be hard for you, but..
不要再给别人寄血了
stop sending people your blood
然后呢 就像“好莱坞性丑闻录“那样
and then, you know, like catch and kill may be?
召开一个完全公开的会议
Or just have like a really open meeting
千万千万 不要开除她
Do not... Don't fire her.
好  -你听说过格丽吗
No?   -Yeah, you know,
她很擅长处理这种情况 我只是..
Gerri would be good on this. And I can..
私下里...给你一点个人建议
I can give you in... some informal advice
如果你愿意接受的话  -我很乐意
if you like.   -I would like that.
我接受
I would.
我很喜欢你
I like you.
你很随和
You're cool.
你不像他们那么清高
You're not judg y, and you... you.
谢谢
Thanks
你开的起玩笑
You can take a joke.
我喜欢
I like that.
和你爹一样
Like your dad.
那可不
Yeah.
你好 小肯  -你好 格雷格
Hey, Kenny.   -Greg, hey
听着 我需要你帮点忙
Listen, I need some help
当然 当然可以  -好
Well, yeah, sure.   -Okay
怎么了 需要我帮你做什么
What do you got? What do you got for me?
我这边有个联络人
I have a contact.
他们一会 会打这个号码找你
They're gonna be calling you on this line
别的吩咐呢  -是这样
Any additional context? Or...   -Yeah, no
你就如实告诉记者真相
You're just telling a journalist the truth.
说大家相处的不愉快
which is that nobody's getting along
公司之间的文化合不来 交易的气氛也很紧张
the two cultures don't mesh, and the deal vibes are bad
好的 放烟雾弹 好给咱们抬价的空间
Okay. Sour the vibes to give us juice in the room.
对 差不多的意思  -没错吧
Yeah, something like that.   -Am I right?
对  -四人突击小分队
Yeah.   -Quad Squad. That.
四人突击小分队最擅长的  -对
It's Quad Squad type shit.   -Yeah
能办到吗  -当然
You can do that?   -Yeah.
那好  -好的
Okay.   -Oh, yeah
杰西 我要你去
Jess, I need you to
联络他们的视觉员  -好 没问题
liaise with their AV guy.   -Yeah. Okay, yeah.
搭一个屏幕
Set up a screening
冬眠 初次剪辑版
Hibernation, rough cut
4K 搞他妈的巨幕 播整整三个小时
Uh, 4 K, fucking giant screen, full three hours
什么时候 是...  -明早
Uh, for when? For...   -Tomorrow morning
没问题
Sure. Yeah.
它苏醒了
It's waking up!
你把我从冬眠状态唤醒
You a woke me from my hibernation.
个个斩杀GoJo成员 像"利刃电子争霸“里一样
Killing off Go Jo members one  -by one like Kali spit ron.
或者"赞娜普拉科斯”
Or Zana plax.
在4DX特效影厅 他们一行动 就会朝你喷水
In 4 DX, they move, they shoot water at you
看到这报道了吗
Hey, you seen this?
对这里的事 恶意抹黑
Nasty little piece about out here?
大家都处得不好 气氛很僵硬
You know, no one getting along, bad vibes.
你知道这人哪传出去的吗
You know where this is coming from?
小西.
Shiv...
肯定是他们说的
Them. I'm sure.
他们可能是想向你们施压
They re probably trying to put the squeeze on you.
你昨晚跟卢卡斯走得还挺近啊
Hear you were getting pretty close with Lukas last night?
怎么 你嫉妒了? 就是
Yeah, you jealous? Just, you know,
找不同切入口 努力推进这交易
working the case, looking for angles.
好吧 有什么有用的消息吗
Right. You get anything we can use?
你要去哪?  -我先回去了
Where you going? Yeah, I'm gonna go back
电影非常有趣
It's so intriguing
说真的 我觉得他是真的想要泛美网科
I mean, honestly, no. I think he wants A TN for real,
他会为此出高价
and he's gonna go high to get it
所以 现在什么计划
So, what's the plan?
上去找他谈 关键时刻  -意向是
Up on the ridge. Crunch time.   -Okay, pitch is,
我们留住泛美网科 在146美元拿下
we retain ATN and we'll bite at 146
或者 他拿走泛美网科 那我们可就要疯狂加价了
Or he takes A TN, but we need a crazy premium.
可以吗  -可以
Goo'd? ?   -Yeah
非常好  -好
Very good.   -Good.
好的  -好
Good.   -Yeah.
很不错  -好了 我们走吧
Good. Great.   -Yeah, let's go
我们上去吧
Let's take it to the ridge
加油
Rock it.
加油 大伙们...  -闭嘴吧
Rock it, fellas...   -Shut... Shut up.
你有听说什么吗 我听说
Oh, what are yoUhearing? I hear that, uh,
希门尼斯觉得他能跳着踢踏舞
Jimenez think s he's gonna be tap dancing
穿越密歇根湖  -你知道
across Lake Michigan.   -You know,
你应该小心点汤姆  -为什么
you should be careful, Tom.   -Why?
这些人摇头丸的药劲快过了 再看看他们的瞳孔
These people are coming down from molly, and their pupils?
都扩散了
They're dilated
看你的鞋 会像是在看太阳
And your shoes are like looking at the sun.
别笑 他们很危险
No, they're dangerous
你在干嘛? 干嘛啊
What are you doing? What are you doing?
你这是怎么了 我是在帮你 汤姆
What are you doing?   -I'm helping you, Tom.
所以大家才不把你当回事儿
This is why people don't take you seriously
因为 你的鞋太他妈白了
'cause your shoes are so fucking white
你的耳垂又厚又有嚼劲
Your earlobes are thick and chewy.
什么鬼  -像藤壶肉
What the fuck?   -Yeah, like barnacle meat
你跟卢卡斯聊得如何
How was your little chat with Lukas
挺好的  -是吗
It was good.   -Yeah.
他这人很无聊 但是很有魅力
I mean, he's boring, but he's very conventionally attractive.
他很魁梧 我以前以为你很魁梧
He's broad. I used to think you were broad.
但你知道的 跟他相比 你就是个瘦猴
but you're, you know, compared to him, you're wiry.
你他妈就像个洞穴探险家
You're like a fucking spe lunker.
操他妈的 真要命
Jesus fucking Christ. Goddamn it.
怎么 他妈的...
What?   -That's some fucking
康纳...是老爸 不 不能说是老爸...就.
Connor... Dad, it's... But it's not Dad... It's..
他妈的发了张照片 真他妈的
Fucking sent a picture. Jesus Christ.
太难过了  -是啊
Oh, I'm sorry.   -Yeah.
你想看看吗
Do you wanna see it?
不 不用了  -好吧
No, I don't.   -Yeah
不看了..它
I don't... Is it...
还好吗
is it okay?
就还好 还好 不是..
No. I mean, yeah, it's fine. It's fine, it's not.
只是...操
It's just...Fuck!
正忙着发酷酷的推文吗
Sending out cool tweet s?
人类真他妈渺小啊 对吧
People are fucking tiny, right?
但 我们除外
But not us. Not us.
谢谢你们发我链接 我看了电影
So, thanks for the link. I saw the movie.
不用客气 那个
Yeah, no worries. You know, it's, uh
只是初剪版本 还在打磨 但…
early cut, still some work, but..
怎么？  -我们很兴奋
Yeah?   -we're excited
会是个大热门  -是吗
It's the big one.   -Oh, yeah?
战略上来说 它必须是
Yeah. I mean, it needs to be, strategically
还有些问题
You know, few issues, but
很令人兴奋  -你知道的
but exciting.   -Yeah. But you know.
一切都很好 “是重点 所以..
Everything is fine " Is the headline, so...
我总感觉 你要接一句" 但是
I feel like there's a " But " In here somewhere.
是的 我是说 电影开始的俩小时
Yeah. I mean, yeah. I mean, the first two hours of the movie
简直像在催眠 但我们会搞定
is a sleeping robot, but we can fix it.
我们有剪辑权 但 真相是
We got control of the cut. But the lowdown is.
就快失控了 明天..
is that it's spiraling and tomorrow, or...
很快就会有媒体报道
soon, there's gonna be a press thing
说“陷入危机" 或者之类的新闻
about it being " In crisis " Or whatever, something like that
好莱坞总是危机四伏 不是吗
You know, Hollywood's always in fucking crisis, right?
是的 没错 没错
Yeah, right. Right
但 这会是大热门
But it's a big one, huh?
是啊 洛杉矶的工作室失控了
Yeah, fucking LA studio's out of control
这是文化问题 但是没问题
It's cultural issues, but, you know, it's cool.
很容易修正 我们只需要
The fix is easy. We only.
我们说出来是要你知道 我们毫无保留
We only flag it so you know we're not hiding.
好的 很感谢 谢谢
All right. I appreciate that. Thanks
那什么 二位
Hey, guys.
你...你们 是来真的吗
Are... are you for real?
什么 那电影
What?   -The movie.
还有他妈的媒体报道 又是怎么回事
And what about these fucking press stories?
你们是不是在搞我
Are you Scooby-Dooing me here?
你们上的学校
Is that where you went?
是他妈汉纳巴贝拉开的商学院吗
Hanna-Barbera fucking business school?
你们到处说 这主题公园的气氛像闹鬼
.. You're telling me the theme parks are haunted
而你们的年度大片烂得像坨屎吗
and your big movie is shitty?
是在故意搞砸这笔交易吗
Are you tanking the deal?
不 不是  -不是
No man. No.  -No.
我们只是开诚布公
We're just being open.
根据我们和银行的模型
Cook on our models and the bank s models
行吧 行吧  -我觉得 需要更高的价格
Yeah, yeah.   -I think there needs to be more value
才能让董事会深信不疑
for the board to get conviction on this
行吧 银行
Right. The banks. Yeah, yeah, yeah
就知道是银行
The banks, of course.
还有节奏问题
Also the pace.
我们..我们需要放慢一点进程
You know, we... we... we might need to slow it down
这是个大项目
a little. It's a behemoth
稍微慢一点
Slow it down a bit.
大选即将到来
And we got the election coming up.
公司也处在过渡期
and then there'll be the transition,
我们也是相关人士 所以
and we have relationships, so, you know,
涉及到监管问题..
in terms of regulatory issues.
我更想跟你们父亲谈交易
Yeah, I preferred doing this with your dad
他是个混蛋 但至少他知道自己要什么
I mean, he was a prick, but at least he knew what he wanted.
等一下 实际上
Okay. Pedant's corner.
我们父亲不是混蛋 好吗
Our dad was not a prick, okay?
行吧 但他确实是
All right, sure. But he was.
只是存在一些问题 这是事实
There are just some issues, is the honest truth
他妈的流媒体 电影公司新闻 很多事情  -行吧
Fucking streamers, studio news, it's a lot.   -Yeah.
我需要尽快搞定这交易
Yeah, I need to make this happen fast
明白吗  -当然 当然
Okay?   -Totally. Totally.
我们全力以赴 但你知道 这是..
We're committed, but, you know, this is a...
这是长跑 不是冲刺
It's a long-distance run. It's not a sprint.
我觉得 他现在要是能看到你俩 一定觉得很丢脸
I think he'd be embarrassed if he saw you two now.
两个大男孩 在这故弄玄虚
His two big boys playing Scooby-Doos
我是不是必须得绕过你们
Am I gonna have to go around you?
直接跟董事会谈
Talk directly to the board?
跟那些老家伙们谈
Talk to the old ones?
真他妈离谱
Unbelievable
罗曼…
Rome...
行
Yeah
我只是在想 你还记得
Hey, I was just thinking. Do you remember
你之前问我 我爸什么时候会死吗
when you asked me when my dad was gonna die?
记得 那是个玩笑 罗曼
Yeah, that was a joke, Roman.
你真是连一周都等不了 对吧
You really couldn't push this a week, could you?
你就是不能
You just couldn't like.
你就完全没有想过
There was no part of you that could just be like.
要不改一下时间吧 因为
" Hey, let's reschedule and move this'cause, you know,
他们的父亲刚去世了
their dad just died and, you know."
我妹妹也…她伤心欲绝
I mean, my sister's kinda... She's fucked up about it,
我哥他手忙脚乱 我自己是魂不守舍
and my brother's a mess, and I'm fucking... I'm gone.
就跟我死了一样 整个世界对我来说都结束了
I'm like I'm on the fucking... I'm dead. It's over for me.
这些没关系 无所谓
It's okay, it's fine.
但你直接把我们吆喝到这地方
But you just drag us out here,
你个没人性的狗东西 你真的
you in human fucking dog man. You...
疯子一个  -兄弟 冷静
Crazy.   -Easy, brother.
你他妈也是杀害他的凶手 你是罪魁祸首
You fucking killed him too. You're the one who did it
你就这么...你把他的生命一点点榨干
You just... And you did. You drained the life out of him.
这点破事 你他妈足足拖了半年
You dragged this thing out for six fucking months
现在你又着急忙慌 把我们叫这来
and then you bring us out here now
两天的时间都等不及
You couldn't wait like a few days.
给我们一点时间过渡都不行吗 你压根没考虑到这个 是吧
You actually couldn't do that for us. No idea, huh?
天哪
God!
说得好 罗曼  -快他妈给我闭嘴吧
This is good, Rome.   -Yeah, shut the fuck up, man.
我们不卖你了 懂吗 交易终止
We're not selling to you. Okay? We're not doing that
我们要耗死你小子
We are gonna grind you down, man
我们会做你的绊脚石
We are sand in the gears
每一封邮件都拖半年再回你
Every e-mail is gonna take like six months
让你泼出去几个亿
We're all gonna spend hundreds of millions of dollars,
最后失去兴趣 自己乖乖走人
and in the end, you're gonna get fucking bored and move on.
这生意没得做了 懂吗
It's not happening, okay?
认真的?  -对
Really?   -Yeah.
对 我他妈恨透你了
Yeah, I fucking hate you.
你要是把我说的话告诉董事会
And if you tell the board I said any of this,
我会说 这些都是谈判策略而已
I'm just gonna say it was a negotiating tactic,
你知道吗 可能这确实是一种计谋
and you know what? Maybe it is.
但这并不是 所以去死吧 混蛋  -等等
But it's not. So fuck you.   -Oh, wait, wait, wait.
你完蛋了   -是吗
You just fucked yourself.   -Did I?
很好  -真的吗
Good.   -Really?
对  -很好
Yeah.   -Good.
你听见你弟弟说什么了吗
Did yoUhear what your little brother said here?
你听见我说的话了吗
Did yoUhear what I said?
你听到了吗  -听清楚了吧
Did yoUhear it? Yeah.   -Was that clear?
你不明白吗
You know, it's uh,
这些不过是谈判技巧而已 傻屌
it's a negotiating tactic, you stupid cunt.
好吧  -的确是这样
All right. Okay.   -It is.
下水道里的屎汤子
You piece of shit!
你应该听到了吧
Did... YoUheard that, right?
跟计划的不一样 但是没准有用
It wasn't the plan, but maybe it plays.
如果在深山老林里跟人谈崩了交易
You know, if a deal collapses in the woods
没有别的人听到 算违反证交所规定吗
and no one hears it, is it an SEC violation?
我感觉他看上去很严肃的样子
All right, I feel like he looks solemn.
可能交易出了问题 说不定已经黄了  -不 肯这个人你是读不懂的
May be danger, may be no deal?   -No, no. Ken's unreadable.
你应该留意罗曼的反应
It's Roman you wanna eyeball
我感觉他们可能成功了
I think they got it over the line.
是找你的吗
You?
你来一下
You.
你好啊
How are you?
感谢来..
Thanks for ca...
伙计们 是马特森
Hey, it's Mattson.
是马特森  -马特森
Mattson.   -Mattson.
好  -怎么了
Yeah. Oh, oh.   -Yeah?
好的
Uh, okay
好的 谢谢
Well, uh, thank you
我很愿意帮忙传达这个消息
Uh, do... I would be glad to pass that message along
你想自己跟他们聊吗
Would you like to speak to one of them yourself?
他们都…
They're both
不用
Nope.
他改价了
Revised offer.
One-ninety-two
涨了五块呢 太棒了
Five-dollar bump, okay
看样子他真的很想要泛美网科
Wow, he really wanted AT N
孩子们 漂亮的本垒打
Hey, it's a home run, boys
向征服者致敬
Hail the conquering heroes
你们的爸爸会为你们感到骄傲的
Your dad would be really proud
192 ?   -不用谢
One-ninety-two?   -You're welcome
太棒了  -是啊
Amazing.   -Yeah, very good
真不错啊  -对
Excellent.   -Yeah.
我们过一下数据 然后提到董事会上吧
Let's run the numbers and take it to the board
好的  -来吧
Right.   - Shall we?
真是太好了  -好啊
Good, good. Yeah, terrific.   -Okay.
192这个数字 无法拒绝
One-ninety-two. It's undeniable.
One-ninety-two
我们来 我们见 我们掠夺
We came, we saw, we pillaged
我们抄了海盗老家
We raided the Vikings.
太棒了  -你在开玩笑吗
Yes!   -Are you kidding me?
192   -干得漂亮 各位
One-ninety-two.   -Great job, guys.
过奖  -谢谢你 杰西
Thanks.   -Thanks, Jess.
喂
Hey.
看样子这桩交易成了
So there's, uh, apparently a deal
是吗  -对 马特森要泛美网科
Deal?   -Yeah, Matsson takes ATN
整个拿下
the whole caboodle
好吧
Okay.
别这样 汤姆 你该高兴高兴
Oh, come on, Tom, you can be happy.
这可是"大逃亡”剧情
It's, you know, it's The Great Escape
再说吧
Well, we'll see
对 走一步看一步
We'll see. Yeah.
泛美网科有一些变动
Yeah, we're looking at some moves at ATN
我不是很满意 所以
I'm not happy, so
好吧
Okay.
你真要这么做吗  -对
You're really gonna do this?   -Yeah
希德跟门肯走得太近了
Cyd's getting too close to Mencken.
对 她真的...
Yeah, she's really just..
自从爸走之后 就太过于热衷权术
She's just a little bit power-crazed post-Dad
得把她弄走
so she's gotta go.
你这么想的吗
You think?
是 你想去跟她说吗
Yeah, you wanna let her know?
可以啊 没问题
Sure. Uh, sure. Yeah.
别太兴奋了汤姆 太奇怪了
Don't get an erection, Tom. It's weird
等我们回去 你想吃晚饭吗
You wanna get dinner when we get back?
这 我也不知道
Well, I don't know
等等 有个重要的电话
Hang on. Important call.
好啊  -你跟你哥哥们在一起吗
Hey.   -Are you with your brothers?
可以给我拍张照 让我看看他们的表情吗
Could you send me a photo of their faces?
当然
Yeah, sure
恭喜 恭喜 恭喜
Congrats, congrats, congrats
什么声音 怎么回事
What... what... what's going on there?
我不知道 这是...  -那是什么
I don't know. It's...   -What is that?
那个 那个是猎杀名单吗
Is that... Is that the kill list?
是的吧  -等等
It is, isn't it?   -Wait.
是 那个 杰西
It's just, uh, Jess managed
弄到了点东西  -果然是的
to get a hold of something.   -Yeah, yes, it is.
这个只是初稿
Um, uh, early draft
GoJo可能需要支付遗散费的名单
GoJo finance list of potential severance costs
只是暂时的版本
It's highly provisional
效用有限 随时可以改动
It's... it's caveat ed, subject to change
只是作为参考
It would just be an interpretation.
少来 格丽 别吊我们胃口了
Come on, Gerri. Don't leave us hanging
上面都有谁
Who's on it?
你们坚持要看的话 那好吧
Okay, if you insist.
没有什么特别的顺序
In seemingly no particular order
潜在的冗余人员
um, just, uh, potentially surplus
包括
to requirements are.
雷  -妈的
Ray.   -God fucking damn it
马克  -操
Mark.   -Shit..
雨果  -该死的北欧佬
Hugo.   -That slalom motherfucker!
弗兰克
Frank.
正常 现在只是猜测而已
Naturally. It's just speculation
卡尔
Karl.
好日子要来了
Let the good times roll
等等 卡洛丽娜呢
Wait, wait. What about Karolina?
我看看
Okay.
她没在上面 会被留下来
She's not on the list, so retained.
留下了 好的  -你呢
Retained. Okay.   -And you?
恭喜恭喜  -谢谢
Congratulations.   -Thank you.
也没在上面
Uh, also not on the list.
汤姆呢 汤姆肯定在上面吧
Tom? What about Tom? Tom must be on the list
我的天
Oh, my God.
我没看见他的名字,  -来这一趟值了
I don't see him.   -Great fucking trip
满载而归
Highly fucking productive
别再说什么被狼养大了 真让人失望
So much for being raised by wolves.
恭喜啊 各位
Congratulations, you guys.
这没什么
Nothing to it. Right?
192   -我们做到了
One-ninety-two.   -We did it